VO DUC DAN

Xô Viết Nghệ Tĩnh street, Bình Thạnh district, Hồ Chí Minh city

6 0972184325 **2** voducdand99@gmail.com **6** https://voducdan.github.io/cv/

SUMMARY

As a Data Engineer, I'm very passionate and dedicated to my work. I'm a hard-working person and always try my best in order to enhance more experience. I have knowledge necessary to make your project a success. I enjoy every step of the design process, from discussion and collaboration to concept and execution, but I find the most satisfaction in seeing the finished product do everything for you that it was created to do.

EDUCATION

HCM University of Science

8/2017 - 10/2021

Bachelor Information Technology

GPA: 7.3/10

WORK EXPERIENCE

Amanotes 6/2021 - Now

Data Engineer

Main responsibilities:

- Investigate, build, and maintain advanced pipelines to handle large volume of data using distributed processing on cloud services
- Design data model for each step in ETL process (from raw to mart layer) to acquire the best performance for data pipeline and provide clean, useful data for DA & DS teams
- Maintain and create new features for internal A/B testing web application
- Crawl/pull data from partners API/Dashboard then transform and load to data warehouse
- Design and implement data lake on google cloud storage to store huge amount of raw event data Technologies: Python, GCP, Airflow, DBT

FPT Software 1/2021 - 7/2021

Data Engineer

Main responsibilities:

- Create data pipeline for extract, transform, load huge data from csv file to data warehouse
- Design and develop data model and schema of data storage for better business insight
- Involve in the process of building the infrastructure required for optimal extraction, transformation, and loading Technologies: Python, GCP, Airflow

Asia Commercial Bank (ACB)

7/2020 - 1/2021

Data Engineer Collaborator

Main responsibilities:

- Setup, maintain big data infrastructure, improve Hadoop cluster by changing YARN schedule method (from FIFO to Fair Scheduler)
- Extract, transform, load raw data from multiple sources to data warehouse both streaming and batch processing
- Crawl and enrich data for analytic purpose

Technologies: Spark, Hadoop, Kafka, Python, SQL

VietMap 9/2019 - 11/2019

Frontend intern

Main responsibilities:

- Build web app to send daily news, product information to client
- Build web app to manage customer

Technologies: Vueis, .NET Framework

SKILLS

Big data

- Hadoop
- Spark

- Kafka

Cloud	- Google Cloud Platform
Database	OracleSQL ServerMongoDBPostgreSQL
Scheduler tool	- Airflow
Operation System	- Linux
Web development	Nodejs (Express Framework)AngularReact.js
Language	- Javascript - C# - Python
Version control	- Git/Github

FOREIGN LANGUAGE

English

REFERENCES

Github: https://github.com/voducdan